- ConversationTopicId: 0326_Prospector_talk
  PlayerPrompt: "@0326_Prospector_talk_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0326_Prospector_talk_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0335_BecomingTheBeast
  PlayerPrompt: "@0335_BecomingTheBeast_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0335_BecomingTheBeast_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0335_Attacked
  PlayerPrompt: "@0335_Attacked_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0335_Attacked_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0336_RangerTenevan_Found
  PlayerPrompt: "@0336_RangerTenevan_Found_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0336_RangerTenevan_Found_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0337_RangerRizal_Found
  PlayerPrompt: "@0337_RangerRizal_Found_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0337_RangerRizal_Found_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0324_Fisher_ExplainHotspots
  PlayerPrompt: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Kazu_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Kazu_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Kazu_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Kazu_T2
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Kazu_T2_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Kazu_T2_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Shang_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Shang_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Shang_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Amis_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Amis_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Amis_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Chioma_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Chioma_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Chioma_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Cosmo_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Cosmo_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Cosmo_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Vinkle_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Vinkle_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Vinkle_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Heyl_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Heyl_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Heyl_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Tapas_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Tapas_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Tapas_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Mabel_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Mabel_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Mabel_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Kojo_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Kojo_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Kojo_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Wang_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Wang_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Wang_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Taehwa_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Taehwa_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Taehwa_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Giri_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Giri_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Giri_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_Wolf_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@03_Wolf_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_Wolf_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
